Robin Hattori

Location: Sapporo, Hokkaido, Japan E-mail: anyrobin224@gmail.com

Phone: (811) 456-7890

linkedin.com/in/Robin-Hattori/
github.com/RobinHattori224/

SUMMARY

Graduate of computer science with experience working across the full-stack of software development. I have built 30+ projects on 7 small teams. I have been working as a Full Stack Web Developer and likewi se a Blockchain developer & Database Administrator for most of the companies I have worked for. I do believe that my experience will benefit your projects. Please feel free to contact me if I can be helpf ul for your projects.

Best Regards, Robin

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering University of Montreal 2010 – 2014 Montreal, QC, Canada

SKILLS

Frontend

React, Vue.js, Angular, Javascript/Typescript, HTML5, SASS, MaterialUI, TailWind CSS, JQuery, Webpack

Backend

Node.js, Python, PHP, C#, Java, Ruby on Rails, AWS APIs, Google Map APIs

Database

MySQL, Mongodb, Redis, POSTgresql, Firebase, Dynamodb, Oracle

Framework

Next, Nuxt, .Net MVC, Flask, Django, YII2, Code Igniter, Laravel, Symphony, Spring

Blockchain

Solidity, Ethereum, Web3.js, Truffle, Hardhat, C/C++, Docker, IPFS, Ether.js, Ganache, Metamask, Solana, Rust, GoLang

Experience

Senior Fullstack Web & Blockchain Developer

Sep 2020 - NOW

YAMAGATA INTECH

Hokkaido, Japan

- Have built Smart Contracts using Solidity to automatically manage uploaded base64-based data sets in the platform
- Have built professional REST APIs for the dashboard and admin portal
- Have deployed the project on the production/staging environment by leveraging services like Ela stic Beanstalk and Route 53 on AWS
- Have implemented core features like the onboarding process and automotive medical reports g eneration using some machine learning algorithms

Senior Fullstack Web & Blockchain Developer

Oct 2019 – Aug 2020

Fenrir Inc

Osaka, Japan

- Providing all phases of the development lifecycle
- Diving into new and complex systems
- Consulting with clients to establish their specific needs in architecture/technology solutions
- Overseeing other engineers, debugging, patching, testing Senior Web Developer & Blockchain de veloper

Senior Software Engineer

Jun 2017 - Sep 2019

WEARE4C

Toronto, Canada

- Developed 7 front-end and back-end applications written in Nuxt
- Developed 5 front-end applications written in React
- Developed and executed 200+ unit tests using Jest
- Collaborated with 30+ colleagues in local and remote locations

Senior Software Engineer

Jun 2016 - May 2017

NYN

Windsor, Canada

- Mentored 3 junior back-end developers on the team on React and developed the marketing web site using React/GraphQL/Typescript and Redux.
- Set up the continuous integration automated test/build system for all engineering teams using B uildBot
- Represented Perficient in 50+ client meetings

Senior FullStack Developer

Sep 2014 - May 2016

NETCOTECH

Edmonton, Canada

- Troubleshooted 2,000+ code-related issues and defects
- Produced detailed design documentation, unit test plans, and documented code for 50+ clients
- Practiced strong configuration management and version control for 20+ projects across 4 teams
- Attended 100+ weekly stand-up meetings to receive tasks and instruction for weekly goals

PROJECTS

Apr 2021 - Nov 2021

IXIRSWAP

- Wrote smart contract using Solidity and wrote xtoken.cafe using React/Web3.js
- Designed privacy aware ChainCoin architecture for the e-commerce implementation
- Integrated ChainCoin interface (staking and yield farming page) using web3 with smart contracts
- ixirswap.com

Jul 2020 - Feb 2021

Sofocle Technologies

- Development frontend using React and web3.js & ethers.js
- Development of smart contracts
- Development of application APIs for the client-side to facilitate the blockchain interaction
- sofocle.com

Mar 2020 - Jun 2020

Aurum Wallet

- Creating web application using React and Redux that communicate with deployed Smart contract using web3.js
- Creating smart contracts with file storage and sharing functionality
- Working on Solidity to develop distributed applications on Ethereum
- Chrome Extension

Aug 2017 - Sep 2019

Tacton Network Management System

- Detected and Fixed 500+ issues
- Built Map Management System using Google Map APIs
- Migrated Data from Zoho to MySQL database using zoho
- www.tacton.com

Apr 2016 - Oct 2016

Support Service for Events in Community

- Built meeting schedule page across continent
- combines hundreds of millions of data points and explores the roots of poverty

- Built service page that help municipalities allocate stations, emergency vehicles, and front-line p ersonnel to reduce risk, improve response times, and save lives
- www.darkhorseanalytics.com

May 2015 - Feb 2016 Galvin Salesforce & Pardot Service System

- Built a responsive web app using Nuxt that support consulting service
- Built Amazon AWS S3 Bucket and connected to Mongo Atlas database
- Built users management interface
- galvintech.com